Vanja Paunovic

Software Engineer

Belgrade, Serbia (+381) 65 541 9360 vana997@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/vpaunovic qithub.com/dzimiks

Summary

I am a passionate, self-motivated and committed computer science student. The majority of my spare time I've spent on learning new algorithms and data structures. I have worked and thrived in a team setting through the internships I have had in the last two years. Learning from my teammates and constantly interacting with clients taught me discipline and it's giving me motivation to progress.

Work History

Data Analyst Consultant

August, 2018 - Present

Telekom Serbia

Parsing logs and analyzing company data using ELK Stack.

Full Stack Engineer

July, 2017 - September, 2017

Startup

Developed MEAN stack web applications.

Created administrator management system for on-site content upload.

Designed and implemented web pages.

Frontend Developer Internship

July, 2016 - September, 2016

Devana Technologies

Worked in small and efficient team.

Education

Bachelor in Computer Science

2016 - present

Union University, Faculty of Computing

High School Diploma

XIV Belgrade Gymnasium

2012 - 2016

Projects

InfViewer - It is a visualization tool for relational data models with CRUD, search and sort functionalities. It works with serial, sequential, index-sequential and database files.

GeKoSeM - Generic document manager. It can be used for organizing and editing documents with textual or graphical editor.

TetrisAI - TetrisAI represents basic Tetris simulation. It was my seminary project for Intelligent systems course.

PanRock Global - Designed complete website and implemented many functionalities.

FEFA - Maintained website and implemented news feed.

Languages

English - Professional working proficiency

Serbian - Native or bilingual proficiency

German - Elementary proficiency (Deutsches Sprachdiplom der Kultusministerkonferenz - A2)

Skills

Java

C/C++

Python

HTML 5

CSS 3

Javascript

Honors And Awards

CodeGovernment, May 2018 (3rd place)

Developed web app with simple UX design and smart search engine which simplifies usage of eGovernment portal.

MatHack, May 2018 (finalist)

Made web app that generates optimal trajectory from starting to ending point on map using machine learning algorithms.

FON Hackathon, April 2018 (1st place)

Developed web application using Big Data. The application goal is to provide data analysis for Telekom Serbia. Solution was distributed cloud-based analysis system and it has interactive data visualization. The system contains a tool for personalized package recommendation, as well as a tool for detecting irregularities of the network in real time.